JESUS BLANCO

WEB DEVELOPER

INFO

PHONE (+58)412-6883874

EMAIL
me@jesusblanco.xyz

LINKS

<u>Twitter</u>

<u>Instagram</u>

<u>Website</u>

SKILLS

HTML & CSS

 $\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet$

JavaScript skills

 $\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$

UI design skills

 $\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ$

User Experience skills

 $\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$

LANGUAGES

Spanish

••••

English

 $\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$

PROFILE

Freelancer junior web developer with two and half years of experience using front-end stacks. I introduce your product to new customers!

My specialty is to create websites for small businesses that want to expand their brand through the internet using a web page as the main way to attract new customers. I use current UI/UX design trends to create pages focused on showing products and services in a minimalist and pleasant way for users combining colors, shadows, layout and animations.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Junior UI Designer and Front-end Developer, White Peak Tech

Miami

Nov 2018 - Present

- Worked as a productive and positive team member in UI/UX design and Front-end developing field.
- Successfully identified, designed and developed client requeriments.
- Worked in multiple projects efficiently.
- Worked to assess competing websites in regards to content, look, and feel.
- Evaluated and became knowledgeable in new standards, technologies, and trends in website development.

Junior UI Designer and Web Developer, MPDieselJU Aug 2018 - Sep 2018

San Cristóbal, VE

- In charge of UI/UX, front-end development and wordpress hosting.
- Effectively translated client requirements into designs requirements.
- Used flat design to make UI.
- Research and development in short time, saving money to the client.
- Provided effective troubleshooting for client requeriments.

EDUCATION

Universidad Nacional Experimental del Táchira, Computer engineering

San Cristóbal, VE

May 2015 - Present

REFERENCES

David Vaisberg from White peak tech

david@whitepeaktech.com